flexiele.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Statement - flexiele

We at FlexiEle are committed to protecting the privacy and information of all those who visit our website and the clients who register to use services that we provide that include mobile applications. You consent to and accept the policies described in this privacy policy when you visit our site.

The policy describes how we at FlexiEle collect, process, use and disclose information that includes your personal information. It also states the choices you have with regards to that information.

## **Types of Personal Information We Collect**

Your information is collected by us in a variety of ways. This includes Personal Data, information that allows someone to directly or indirectly identify you and contact you. This includes your name, email address and phone number that you may choose to provide us.

In addition, we may observe your preferences, activities, transactions and other connection and computer information that relates to your use of our website and services. This includes information such as IP addresses which allows us to know where you are located geographically.

## How FLEXIELE Uses This Personal Information

FlexiEle utilizes the Personal Information you provide us to:

  * Send you communications with regards to marketing and various business, service and product offers from FlexiEle . These offers are based on the business characteristics, interests and locations you have disclosed to us or we have observed.
  * Send you surveys and information about promotional events.
  * Decide your eligibility for certain offers.
  * Provide you with more information that you may find interesting such as newsletters, announcements and bulletins.
  * Manage our day-to-day business needs which include but are not limited to product development, website administration, contract management, payment processing, security and fraud prevention, financial account management, reporting and legal compliance, corporate governance, business continuity and analytics.

## Disclosure

FlexiEle does not share, sell, rent, or trade personal information collected through its websites with third parties for their sole promotional purposes or as otherwise outlined in this Privacy Statement.

## Situations in which We Disclose Your Personal Information

We at FlexiEle are cognizant of the fact that you do not desire your Personal Information to be released to third parties for their marketing purposes. This is how we limit our sharing of your Personal Information:

  * Your Personal Information may be shared with our affiliates by us. This will only be for the purposes outlined above.
  * Your Personal Information may be shared with our service providers. These service providers are bound by contract or law to protect your Personal Information. They will only use your Personal Information as per our instructions.
  * Where needed, your Personal Information may be disclosed by us to affect the transfer or sale of our business assets, protect our property, enforce our rights or for the protection of the rights, property or safety of others.
  * As mentioned above, when required by law to disclose your Personal Information, we will always do so. T This includes instances such as a response to a subpoena. We will disclose this information when required by law to courts and law enforcement agencies .
  * Information about you that is not personally identifiable may be disclosed by us. This could include statistical and/or aggregated data about our clients that we publish in reports. No one will be able to identify, locate or contact you through the information in these reports. There is also no identifiable company information in these reports.

## Cookies

We collect certain transnational information when you visit our website. We do so through the use of cookies. Cookies are tiny text files sent to your computer or device by the websites you visit. They can store information in your browser settings or uniquely identify your browser. We utilize cookies to help us identify and recognize you when you return to our website. If you do not wish for cookies to be stored in your browser, you can visit the help section on your browser to determine how to change your browser settings.

## Privacy Policy for Client Employees

We at FlexiEle are committed to ensuring that the privacy and security of all the Personal Information we collect to service our clients is protected. Our clients provide us with their employees’ Personal Information that includes names, email addresses, phone numbers, date of birth, unique identification numbers and payroll data. Here we state our practices with respect to all of the Personal Information provided to us by our clients.

Your Personal Information will be collected and processed by FlexiEle only as per instructions and permissions given to us by our client (the employer) or you. At all times, appropriate and reasonable security controls are maintained by FlexiEle to protect your information.

Your Personal Information will be disclosed to the employer and to other entities when the employer gives such instructions. In addition, whenever the law requires us to, we will disclose Personal Information. This includes instances such as a response to a subpoena. We will disclose this information when required by law to courts and law enforcement agencies in the United States and other countries where we have our operations.

When an employee logs on to our software, we track their IP address, operating system and device based on our client’s (the employer’s) instructions. This data is shared only with our client.

For any questions with respect to your privacy rights, please get in touch with your employer’s human resources department.

## Android Functions Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is required as the app uses the microphone, contacts and telephony features, hence the android.permission.RECORD_AUDIO permission, android.permission.READ_PHONE_STATE permission, and android.permission.GET_ACCOUNTS permission.

## How to Contact us

Please contact us if you have any questions, comments or complaints if you believe that FlexiEle has not handled your Personal Information properly or that it has breached its privacy obligations, your complaint may be directed at [info@FlexiEle.com](mailto:info@FlexiEle.com)
